{
    "subject": "resource/Martinetes",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Flamenco_styles",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Martinetes is Flamenco styles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.883775532245636,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in Flamenco styles like Martinetes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8741058111190796,
            "question": "What makes Martinetes unique within Flamenco styles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8651216626167297,
            "question": "What kind of styles are Martinetes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8538996577262878,
            "question": "Are there different regional variations of Flamenco styles like Martinetes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5406895279884338,
            "question": "Can you give me an example of a Flamenco style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42407944798469543,
            "question": "What other musical genres are influenced by Flamenco?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38012969493865967,
            "question": "Is Flamenco a type of music or dance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33185502886772156,
            "question": "What instruments are typically used in Flamenco music?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.30669036507606506,
            "question": "Where did Flamenco originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2465425431728363,
            "question": "How does Martinetes influence modern dance and music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Martinetes is Flamenco styles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7623_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Flamenco originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7623_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments are typically used in Flamenco music?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7623_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Flamenco a type of music or dance?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7623_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7623_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that the subject of Martinetes is related to Flamenco styles. This can be seen from various descriptions in the text, such as its origin from forges and its classification under flamenco modalities like ton\u00e1s and cantes grandes."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}